// cretaing an array and passing numbers, questions, options and answers
let questions=[
    {
        numb:1,
        question: "Who was known as Iron man of India?",
        answers: "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel",
        options: [
            "Govind Ballabh Pant",
            "Jawaharlal Nehru",
            "Subhash Chandra Bose",
            "Sardar Vallabhbhai Patel"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:2,
        question: "The Indian to beat the computers in mathematical wizardry is",
        answers: "Shakunthala Devi",
        options: [
            "Ramanujam",
            "Rina Panigrahi",
            "Raja Ramanna",
            "Shakunthala Devi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:3,
        question: "Professor Amartya Sen is famous in which of the fields?",
        answers: "Economics",
        options: [
            "Biochemistry",
            "Electronics",
            "Economics",
            "Geology"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:4,
        question: "Which of the following was Satyajit Ray associated with?",
        answers: "Film Direction",
        options: [
            "Classical music",
            "Commercial art",
            "Film Direction",
            "Classical dance"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:5,
        question: "Amjad Ali Khan is associated with which of the following musical instruments?",
        answers: "Sarod",
        options: [
            "Veena",
            "Sarod",
            "Violin",
            "Sitar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:6,
        question: "Ms. Bachendri Pal had undertaken a unique expedition for focusing attention on which of these?",
        answers: "Sprit of Adventure",
        options: [
            "One Nation one Family",
            "The Girl Child",
            "National Integration",
            "Sprit of Adventure"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:7,
        question: "R. K. Laxman is a renowned",
        answers: "Cartoonist",
        options: [
            "Dance master",
            "Writer",
            "Cartoonist",
            "Journalist"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:8,
        question: "Who is the Flying Sikh of India?",
        answers: "Milkha singh",
        options: [
            "Mohinder Singh",
            "Joginder Singh",
            "Milkha singh",
            "Ajit Pal Singh"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:9,
        question: "Bismillah Khan was associated with?",
        answers: "Shehnai",
        options: [
            "Sarod",
            "Shehnai",
            "Flute",
            "Tabla"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb:10,
        question: "Who is known as the 'Lady with the Lamp'?",
        answers: "Florence Nightingale",
        options: [
            "Florence Nightingale",
            "Sarojini Naidu",
            "Indira Gandhi",
            "Joan of Arc"
        ]
    },
    
]